govarrestrecords.com 2011-09-03

# GovArrestRecords.com - Comprehensive Online Arrest and Warrent Records Searches

This privacy policy sets out how GovArrestRecords.com uses and protects any information that you give GovArrestRecords.com when you use this website. GovArrestRecords.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

GovArrestRecords.com  may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

        whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

        if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us right  here.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
